# Gurinder Nanda



**Profile** 

**Skills** 

37 Byron Avenue Takapuna, Auckland, 0622

Mobile: 022 329 9794

EMAIL: <a href="mailto:lovey\_nanda2000@yahoo.com">lovey\_nanda2000@yahoo.com</a>

I am a highly motivated person with 4+ years of experience in customer service. As world being tech savvy, I have decided to move into IT industry, and I am currently pursuing qualifications in Information & Technology. With ongoing studies, I am seeking for a job opportunity in an organization where I can gain IT knowledge and get some industry experience and make myself useful to the organization. I am exceptionally energetic, self-motivated and always have willingness to learn new things. I enjoy a challenge and always have a 'can do' attitude plus excellent communication skills.

#### **Technical skills:**

- 1. MCSA: Windows Server 2012 r2
- 2. Basic Knowledge of HTML. CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap (working towards advanced level)
- 3. Familiar with Insightly CRM, Skills to quickly grasp other business specific tools and software's.
- 4. Good Knowledge of MS Office, MS Word, MS PowerPoint, MS Excel, Opera and familiar with MYOB.

### Communication and customer service skills

1. Very good at communication, level of spoken and written English is very good.

## **Management and Leadership skills**

- 2. Managed a small team of concierges at The Sentinel.
- 3. Got leadership qualities and can manage and lead others with examples.
- 4. Ability to grasp new things and work in team.

# Work Experience

#### **The Sentinel** / Concierge (Part-time)

February 2015 - Present, AUCKLAND

Working closely with the Property Manager to ensure ongoing success of day to day operations and full understanding of Security System, fire evacuation policies and procedures, health and safety regulations.

### Countdown Supermarket / Supervisor

January 2014 - February 2016, AUCKLAND

Manage Auto-stocks, Achieving Sales target and boost sales, Health and safety management, Stock Management, Inventory control, Marketing of New products, Promotional Management, Roaster staff.

#### **Hotel Aman / Front Office Executive**

February 2012 - March 2013, INDIA

Meet and Greet Guests, Accommodate Guest's special requests, Aware of the Hotel Reservation System, and cancellation policy, Action the Housekeeping reports immediately upon receipt, record discrepancies and report to the shift leader.

### Education

Aspire2International / Graduate Diploma in Information Technology

(Level 7), AUCKLAND

Currently pursuing

# **Microsoft Certified Solution Associate (MCSA)**: Windows Server 2012 R2

- MCSA, 410: Installing and Configuring Windows Server 2012
- MCSA, 411: Administering Windows Server 2012
- MCSA, 412: Configuring Advanced Windows Server 2012 Services

### **Ntec** / Diploma in Business Management (Level 7)

January 2014 - November 2014, AUCKLAND

### Kumaun University / Bachelor of Commerce

2010 - 2013, Nainital, U.K., INDIA

# **Aptech Computer Institute**/ Accounts Pro - Computerized financial accounting

2011 – 2011, Rudrapur, U.K., INDIA

#### Holy Child School / Year 10 - Year 12

2008 - 2010, Rudrapur, U.K., INDIA

#### References

1. Stewart Jay (Head Concierge), The Sentinel, Takapuna

Email: headconcierge@thesentinel.co.nz

Mobile: 021 265 8324 (work) 021 070 5580 (personal)

# 2. Sunny Handa (Systems Administrator), AIA Insurance

Email: handa\_gur@hotmail.com

Mobile: 029 488 8822